gotchamovies.com 2015-04-02

# Privacy Policy | GotchaMovies

GotchaMovies.com cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [Privacy@GotchaMovies.com](mailto:Privacy@GotchaMovies.com)

## Information Collection and Use by GotchaMovies.com

GotchaMovies.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send newsletters, updates and notifications to users relating to the GotchaMovies.com service. GotchaMovies.com also collects other profile data in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other including but not limited to musical interests, gender, age, location and occupation.

GotchaMovies.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information, such as IP address and browser type, from all users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services.

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the GotchaMovies.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join GotchaMovies.com , to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, personal messages, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on GotchaMovies.com with each other through the GotchaMovies.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members.

From time to time, GotchaMovies.com or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from.

## Member Invitations

GotchaMovies.com members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. GotchaMovies.com stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. GotchaMovies.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders, and notifications of member services (such as messages from other members). Recipients of invitations from GotchaMovies.com may contact GotchaMovies.com to request the removal of this information from our database.

## Use of Cookies

GotchaMovies.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes such as ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information.

## Links

GotchaMovies.com contains links to other sites. GotchaMovies.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on GotchaMovies.com .

## Reviews, WebLogs, Lists, and Public Forums

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Reviews, WebLogs, Lists or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by people to send you unsolicited communications.

## Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

GotchaMovies.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info.

## Email Choice/Opt-out

Members who no longer wish to receive email newsletters, updates or notifications may choose not to by following the opt-out instructions contained in such email newsletters, updates or notifications.

## Third Party Advertising

Ads appearing on the GotchaMovies.com site may be delivered to users by GotchaMovies.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time you are served an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by GotchaMovies.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Children Under Age 13

GotcahMovies.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for or send any information about yourself to GotcahMovies.com, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on GotcahMovies.com. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

## Security

GotchaMovies.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. GotchaMovies.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on GotchaMovies.com , please contact us at [Privacy@GotchaMovies.com](mailto:Privacy@GotchaMovies.com) .

## Sharing and Disclosure of Information GotchaMovies.com collects

Except as described above, GotchaMovies.com will not disclose personal information to any third party without a user's explicit permission, unless otherwise required by law. GotchaMovies reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of GotchaMovies.com or the transfer of substantially all of its assets to a successor in interest.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: [Info@GotchaMovies.com](mailto:Info@GotchaMovies.com)

Group content visibility:
